http://www.olympicdairy.com/termsofuse

Trigger
Sign up Newsletter
Join YourStore's squad for 20% off
and get all the latest news, trends and offs and offers straight to your inbox. Or get 15% off using code SQUAD15
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
1 UK only; 2. Offar expiras 23:59(GMT) 10/02/16; 3.
FAQ
Contact us
FR
Products
Why Organic?
Recipes
About us
Home
Why Organic?
TERMS OF USE
Ultima Foods Inc. and its affiliates (collectively “Ultima”) welcome you to this
website (the “Website”). Ultima is a company having its head office located
at 4600 Armand-Frappier St. in Saint-Hubert, Québec, J3Z 1G5, Canada.
By accessing or using this Website, or downloading any part of its content,
you agree to be bound by all the terms of use set out below (the “Terms of
Use”), which Terms of Use constitute a contract between you and Ultima
governing your use of the Website. This contract does not apply to any
purchase or other contractual relation that may exist between you and
Ultima. Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using the Website. If
you do not accept these Terms of Use, please do not access the Website or its
content.
Amendment to the Terms of Use
Ultima may modify all or part of the Terms of Use at its discretion, at any time
and without prior notice. Any changes will be effective upon being posted on
the Website. Your use of the Website will be subject to the most current
version of the Terms of Use posted. In the event of a conflict between an
amendment and an earlier version of the Terms of Use, the most recent
version containing the amendments shall prevail. Please consult these Terms
of Use regularly. If you do not accept the updates to the Terms of Use, please
immediately discontinue your use of the Website.
Personal Information
To access certain functions of the Website, you may be asked to provide
personal information. Personal information collected through this Website is
used and disclosed in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy, which
is incorporated into these Terms of Use. To read our privacy policy, click here.
All information you provide on this Website must be correct, current and
complete and must not be provided by minors. Furthermore, you represent
and warrant that you will not use another person’s name in connection with
the use of this Website.
Intellectual Property
All rights, titles and interests in and to the Website are the exclusive property
of Ultima. The Website is protected under applicable intellectual property
laws, including, without limitation, the Copyright Act and the Trade-marks Act
as well as all other applicable laws pertaining to intellectual property. You are
not authorized to (i) copy, amend, reproduce, publicly post, transmit, sell or
otherwise exploit or use all or part of the Website content, (ii) use or distribute Website elements for commercial purposes, or (iii) create derivative
works or websites using the Website content.
The trademarks, logos, service marks and distinguishing guises displayed on
this Website (collectively, the “Trademarks”) are registered Trademarks
owned by Ultima or belonging to Ultima by virtue of use under common law,
or are otherwise used by Ultima under licence with their owner’s permission.
Any reproduction or use of any Trademark without the prior express written
consent of Ultima is prohibited. No information or other content on this
Website should be construed as directly or indirectly granting any
authorization or right whatsoever to use any of the Trademarks without the
prior written permission of Ultima or such other party that may own the
Trademarks.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, you may copy, privately display, and, from
time to time, print a paper copy of pages contained on this Website solely for
your personal and non-commercial use. You must retain all copyright and
Trademark notices and any other proprietary notices appearing on this
Website. If you breach any of these Terms of Use, your authorization to use
this Website or the services offered thereon automatically terminates and you
must immediately destroy any downloaded or printed materials.
Prohibited Uses
You agree not to do the following:
impersonate or misrepresent your relationship with any person or entity;
access and/or use sections of the Website or Ultima’s computer systems that are not public;
attempt to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of the Website or any
related system or network, or breach any security or authentication
measures used in connection with the Website or any related system
or network;
modify, move, delete or otherwise add any element to the Website,
attempt to decrypt, decompile, disassemble, reverse engineer, use or
restrict any of the software used to provide the Website;
harm or threaten to harm other Website users in any way or interfere
with, or attempt to interfere with, the access of any user, host or
network, including, without limitation, by sending a virus or by means
of overloading, flooding, spamming or mailbombing; and
use the Website in an abusive way contrary to its intended use, the
documentation pertaining thereto or Ultima’s reasonable instructions.
Ultima has the right to investigate any violation of these Terms of Use and
initiate proceedings in this regard, including, without limitation, for
3
infringements of any intellectual property rights or security breaches, the
whole in accordance with applicable laws. Ultima may involve and cooperate
with law enforcement authorities in order to initiate proceedings against
users who violate these Terms of Use. You acknowledge that, although Ultima
has no obligation to monitor your access to or use of the Website, it has the
right to do so in connection with the operation of the Website in order to
ensure your compliance with these Terms of Use, or in order to comply with
applicable laws or the orders or requirements of a court, administrative
agency, or any other government body.
Third Party Information and Hyperlinks
Although Ultima monitors the information contained on the Website, some of
the information on the Website may be supplied by independent third parties.
While Ultima makes every effort to ensure the accuracy of all information
contained on the Website, Ultima cannot warrant the accuracy of any such information.
The Website contains links to access other websites that are not under the
control of Ultima. These links are provided to you for convenience only, it
being understood that Ultima does not endorse any of these other websites.
Ultima assumes no liability regarding the content of any website whatsoever
to which this Website gives access nor does Ultima make any representation
of any kind whatsoever regarding the quality of any product or service
offered on such websites.
Ultima assumes no liability and offers no warranty of accuracy, security or
otherwise in regards to the content (including opinions) provided by the
public on this Website or any other website, nor does it endorse such content.
Nutritional information
Subjects related to nutrition or health may be discussed on the Website, but
they must not be interpreted as professional advice. Always consult a
nutritionist or a health care professional before making any changes to your
diet.
Anonymous Information Gathered through the Website
Ultima gathers anonymous information respecting the use of its Website.
Thus, Ultima uses various technological tools to know which pages of its
Website have been consulted by visitors, to determine the frequency with
which hyperlinks are used and to compile statistics on visitors and their use
of the Website. This information is gathered by means of an analytical platform (such as: Google Analytics), log files and cookies. This anonymous information is gathered in such a way that Ultima is unable to identify you.
Ultima may post advertisements based on areas of interest on this Website,
which is owned by Ultima, as well as on the other websites it operates and on
any other third-party websites, using the anonymous information gathered
when you consult this Website. Advertising campaigns based on areas of
interest, which are sometimes referred to as personalized or targeted
advertising campaigns, are displayed based on the anonymous information
gleaned from your activities on the Website and from any other websites you
may have visited that posted content or advertising campaigns from Ultima.
Like other online advertising networks, Ultima uses cookies, web beacons
(also known as web bugs) and other technologies (collectively, the “ Cookies ”). Cookies allow Ultima to determine which advertisements you
see, which advertisements you click on and the other things you do when you
consult the Website. This allows Ultima to offer you more useful and relevant
advertising. For example, if Ultima is able to know what advertising is
presented to you, it can avoid showing you the same advertising repeatedly.
Ultima does not connect your activities on third-party websites to your
identity when Ultima offers you advertisements based on areas of interest.
Advertisers or advertising agencies working on their behalf sometimes use
various technological tools to send the advertising campaigns that appear on
our Website directly to your web browser. To do so, they automatically obtain
your IP address. They can also use Cookies to measure the efficiency of their
advertising campaigns and to personalize advertising content. Ultima has no
access to or control over these Cookies or other technological tools that thirdparty advertisers or websites might use.
Generally, you may choose not to receive personalized advertising
campaigns from third-party advertisers and advertising networks that are
members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or that subscribe to the
Canadian Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising by
visiting the opt-out page of the websites of the NAI and the Digital
Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can also disable Google Analytics for Display
Advertising and customize the advertisements displayed on the Google
Display Network via the Ads Settings page (link).
Solicitation
Providing Ultima with your email address or telephone number indicates that
you consent to Ultima contacting you by phone or email. This consent
authorizes Ultima to send you any information regarding the Website, to
inform you of other products, services and opportunities that may interest
you and to get your opinion on the quality of the Website.
If you no longer wish to be contacted by Ultima, you may send a written request to Ultima at the following address:
By email, click here
By mail:
Ultima Foods Inc.
Consumer Response
4600 Armand-Frappier Street,
Saint-Hubert, Québec
J3Z 1G5
Communications Directed to Ultima
Please note that Ultima does not solicit nor does it wish to receive any ideas,
suggestions, documents or any other information of any kind whatsoever in
connection with the development, design, manufacture, modification or
marketing of its products or any new product unless it specifically invites the
public to submit its ideas in the context of an open innovation challenge that
Ultima may organize from time to time.
Please also note that all information (including your ideas) other than
personal information that you may provide to Ultima will be considered as
non-confidential such that Ultima shall be free to use it for any purpose,
including, but without limitation, for the development, creation and marketing
of new products.
LIMITATION OF WARRANTY
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE USING THIS WEBSITE AT YOUR OWN RISK
AND THAT ALL INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS-IS”
AND “AS-AVAILABLE” BASIS. TO THE FULL EXTENT ALLOWED UNDER
APPLICABLE LAW, ULTIMA AND ITS SUPPLIERS DO NOT GUARANTEE THE
ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON OR
THROUGH THE WEBSITE, AND THEY MAKE NO REPRESENTATION AS REGARDS
THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING THAT THE WEBSITE WILL MEET YOUR NEEDS OR BE
COMPATIBLE WITH EQUIPMENT OR SOFTWARE PROVIDED BY A THIRD PARTY,
THAT THE WEBSITE WILL NOT BE INTERRUPTED, THAT IT WILL BE FREE FROM
PROBLEMS OR ERRORS OR THAT ALL ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED. THE
INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE MAY BE OUT OF DATE, AND ULTIMA MAKES
NO COMMITMENT WITH RESPECT TO ITS ACCURACY. ULTIMA MAY
PERIODICALLY ADD, CHANGE, IMPROVE OR UPDATE THE INFORMATION ON
THE WEBSITE WITHOUT NOTICE. ULTIMA MAY REFER TO PRODUCTS,
PROGRAMS OR SERVICES THAT ARE NOT AVAILABLE IN YOUR REGION. YOU
UNDERSTAND THAT ULTIMA CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE OR
WARRANT THAT FILES AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOADING FROM THE INTERNET WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES, COMPUTER WORMS, TROJAN HORSES OR OTHER
CODE THAT MAY MANIFEST CONTAMINATING OR DESTRUCTIVE PROPERTIES.
ULTIMA DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT ITS WEBSITE OR EMAILS
SENT FROM THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE FROM VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL
COMPONENTS.
TO THE FULL EXTENT ALLOWED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ULTIMA’S WARRANTIES
AND REMEDIES EXPRESSLY SET FORTH HEREIN (IF ANY) ARE EXCLUSIVE AND
REPLACE ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, BE THEY EXPLICIT OR IMPLIED EITHER IN
FACT OR BY OPERATION OF LAW, ALL DUTIES, ALL ORAL OR WRITTEN
STATEMENTS, OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, AVAILABILITY, PERFORMANCE,
COMPATIBILITY, SUITABILITY FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE,
SATISFACTORINESS, COMPLIANCE WITH DESCRIPTION, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, ALL OF WHICH ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
TO THE FULL EXTENT ALLOWED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL
ULTIMA OR ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, PARTNERS OR LICENSORS, OR ANY OF
THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, CONSULTANTS,
AGENTS OR SUPPLIERS HAVE ANY LIABILITY, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT,
DELICT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR STRICT LIABILITY, FOR INCIDENTAL
(INCLUDING LEGAL FEES), DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, OR
PUNITIVE DAMAGES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, OR FOR LOSS OF REVENUE
OR PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES, LOSS OR CORRUPTION OF,
OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, OR DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION OR DATA,
OR FOR ANY OTHER FINANCIAL LOSS ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
WITH THE USE, PERFORMANCE, FAILURE, OR INTERRUPTION OF THE WEBSITE,
WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE, EVEN IF ULTIMA HAD BEEN ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IF ULTIMA IS FOUND LIABLE TO PAY YOU
DAMAGES, ULTIMA’S TOTAL CUMULATIVE LIABILITY TO YOU HEREUNDER
SHALL NOT EXCEED CDN$100, UNLESS PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Ultima and its affiliates,
suppliers, partners and licensors, and each of their respective directors,
officers and employees from and against any claims, liabilities, damages,
losses, and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and
accounting fees, that are in any way connected to your access to or use of
the Website.
Website Access Refusal or Interruption
Ultima may refuse or interrupt your access to its Website for any reason at its
sole discretion, including where Ultima believes you have violated these
Terms of Use. You agree that Ultima shall not be liable to you or to any other
person whomsoever if your access to the Website is refused or interrupted.
Applicable Law
These Terms of Use shall be governed and construed in accordance with the
laws of the Province of Québec and the federal laws of Canada applicable
therein without regard to any principles of conflict of laws. The courts of the
Province of Québec shall have exclusive jurisdiction over all disputes. The
parties hereby irrevocably submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of the
district of Montreal, Province of Québec.
Severability
If a particular provision of these Terms of Use is held to be invalid by a court
of competent jurisdiction, such provision shall be deemed severed from these
Terms of Use and shall not affect the validity of these Terms of Use as a
whole.
Entire Agreement
These Terms of Use constitute the complete and entire agreement between
the parties as to the use of the Website and they supersede all prior
communications, proposals or agreements between you and Ultima regarding
this Website.
No Waiver
Ultima shall not be considered to have waived any of its rights or remedies
described in these Terms of Use unless the waiver is in writing and signed by
Ultima. No delay or omission by Ultima in exercising its rights or remedies
shall be construed as a waiver of its right to enforce such rights or remedies
at any time.
Contacting Ultima
If you have any concerns, questions, or complaints regarding these Terms of
Use, please contact Ultima: click here.
These Terms of Use were last updated on February 21, 2020.
Yogurts and dairy products made in Canada
Privacy Policy - Terms of use© 2020 Olympic / All rights reserved - DESIGN by LG2 / DEVELOPMENT by CIDMA
Subscribe to our newsletter
Top of the page
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
We use cookies and other technologies to optimize your experience on our website. By continuing to use this site, you agree to the use of cookies by Aliments Ultima Inc, its brands and partners. For more information, please read our terms of use
and our privacy policy.
Agree
Subscribe to our newsletter!
Name *Required field
E-mail *Required field
